http://www.bresslergroup.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting Bresslergroup.com and for reading our privacy policy, which tells you how we use the information we collect.
Bresslergroup does not collect personally identifiable information through our website, unless you choose to voluntarily submit that information through an email or form. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner — for example to add you to our mailing list.
In an effort to improve and personalize your experience on our website, we do collect general information, such as browser types and IP addresses, through the use of cookies and other embedded code. This generates data about how you are using the site, including which pages you visited most frequently, and for what length of time.
We do use remarketing services to advertise Bresslergroup across the Internet. Remarketing targets ads to you based on your prior use of our site and allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs. If you do not wish to participate in our remarketing efforts, you can opt out by visiting http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/.
Bresslergroup does not sell, share, or distribute customer information to any third party organization.
This privacy policy was put into place on January 4, 2016. We reserve the right to change it at any time, as we determine to be appropriate. If you have questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact webmaster@Bresslergroup.com.
